{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549455436742","data":{"timestamp":" 1549455436741"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_151651"," gameId":" 227c6501-69e5-4196-b262-b67a29523609"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kusoma kusoma"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSOMA"," userResponse":" KUSOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549455437713","data":{"timestamp":" 1549455437712"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_151651"," gameId":" 227c6501-69e5-4196-b262-b67a29523609"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kusoma kusoma"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSOMA"," userResponse":" KUSOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549455440630","data":{"timestamp":" 1549455440629"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_151651"," gameId":" 227c6501-69e5-4196-b262-b67a29523609"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunataka macho yaone"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNATAKA"," userResponse":" KUNATAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549455441166","data":{"timestamp":" 1549455441166"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_151651"," gameId":" 227c6501-69e5-4196-b262-b67a29523609"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunataka macho yaone"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MACHO"," userResponse":" MACHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549455441810","data":{"timestamp":" 1549455441809"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_151651"," gameId":" 227c6501-69e5-4196-b262-b67a29523609"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunataka macho yaone"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAONE"," userResponse":" YAONE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549455445902","data":{"timestamp":" 1549455445902"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_151651"," gameId":" 227c6501-69e5-4196-b262-b67a29523609"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Masikio yasikie"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASIKIO"," userResponse":" MASIKIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549455446837","data":{"timestamp":" 1549455446836"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_151651"," gameId":" 227c6501-69e5-4196-b262-b67a29523609"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Masikio yasikie"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YASIKIE"," userResponse":" YASIKIE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549455450507","data":{"timestamp":" 1549455450506"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_151651"," gameId":" 227c6501-69e5-4196-b262-b67a29523609"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mdomo useme"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549455451303","data":{"timestamp":" 1549455451303"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_151651"," gameId":" 227c6501-69e5-4196-b262-b67a29523609"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mdomo useme"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MDOMO"," userResponse":" MDOMO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549455452284","data":{"timestamp":" 1549455452284"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_151651"," gameId":" 227c6501-69e5-4196-b262-b67a29523609"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mdomo useme"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USEME"," userResponse":" USEME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549455456195","data":{"timestamp":" 1549455456195"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_151651"," gameId":" 227c6501-69e5-4196-b262-b67a29523609"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kusoma kusoma"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSOMA"," userResponse":" KUSOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549455457172","data":{"timestamp":" 1549455457171"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_151651"," gameId":" 227c6501-69e5-4196-b262-b67a29523609"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kusoma kusoma"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSOMA"," userResponse":" KUSOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549455460150","data":{"timestamp":" 1549455460149"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_151651"," gameId":" 227c6501-69e5-4196-b262-b67a29523609"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunataka macho yaone"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNATAKA"," userResponse":" KUNATAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549455460695","data":{"timestamp":" 1549455460694"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_151651"," gameId":" 227c6501-69e5-4196-b262-b67a29523609"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunataka macho yaone"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MACHO"," userResponse":" MACHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549455461352","data":{"timestamp":" 1549455461351"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_151651"," gameId":" 227c6501-69e5-4196-b262-b67a29523609"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunataka macho yaone"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAONE"," userResponse":" YAONE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549455465512","data":{"timestamp":" 1549455465511"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_151651"," gameId":" 227c6501-69e5-4196-b262-b67a29523609"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Masikio yasikie"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASIKIO"," userResponse":" MASIKIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549455466446","data":{"timestamp":" 1549455466445"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_151651"," gameId":" 227c6501-69e5-4196-b262-b67a29523609"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Masikio yasikie"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YASIKIE"," userResponse":" YASIKIE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549455470161","data":{"timestamp":" 1549455470160"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_151651"," gameId":" 227c6501-69e5-4196-b262-b67a29523609"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mdomo useme"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549455470958","data":{"timestamp":" 1549455470957"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_151651"," gameId":" 227c6501-69e5-4196-b262-b67a29523609"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mdomo useme"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MDOMO"," userResponse":" MDOMO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549455471944","data":{"timestamp":" 1549455471943"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_151651"," gameId":" 227c6501-69e5-4196-b262-b67a29523609"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mdomo useme"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USEME"," userResponse":" USEME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549455475269","data":{"timestamp":" 1549455475268"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_151651"," gameId":" 227c6501-69e5-4196-b262-b67a29523609"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Na mdomo useme"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549455475381","data":{"timestamp":" 1549455475381"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_151651"," gameId":" 227c6501-69e5-4196-b262-b67a29523609"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mdomo useme"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USEME"," userResponse":" USEME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549455502353","data":{"timestamp":" 1549455502353"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_151651"," gameId":" 227c6501-69e5-4196-b262-b67a29523609"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Na mdomo useme"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549455502423","data":{"timestamp":" 1549455502423"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_151651"," gameId":" 63eda097-5e85-4aa0-82d3-bc127c8de442"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Usiku mmoja Sungura alimtembelea Jimbi na familia yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549455556518","data":{"timestamp":" 1549455556518"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_151651"," gameId":" 2d523ab5-c246-49ee-bd12-cb8b3e7d6e6d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" moto_moto-nyama-nyama-kabla"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" moto"," userResponse":" moto"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549455626191","data":{"timestamp":" 1549455626191"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_151651"," gameId":" 2d523ab5-c246-49ee-bd12-cb8b3e7d6e6d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" moto_moto-nyama-nyama-kabla"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549455626278","data":{"timestamp":" 1549455626278"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_151651"," gameId":" 2d523ab5-c246-49ee-bd12-cb8b3e7d6e6d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walifanya kazi zao zote ____________."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ____________"," userResponse":" USIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-O.rand.30__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549455638841","data":{"timestamp":" 1549455638840"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_151651"," gameId":" 558dba72-b69b-45a3-8472-3c1130f6f088"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-O.rand.30__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" OVAROLI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OVAROLI"," userResponse":" OVAROLI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-O.rand.30__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549455649288","data":{"timestamp":" 1549455649288"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_151651"," gameId":" 558dba72-b69b-45a3-8472-3c1130f6f088"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-O.rand.30__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" OVAROLI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OVAROLI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-O.rand.30__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549455650904","data":{"timestamp":" 1549455650903"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_151651"," gameId":" 558dba72-b69b-45a3-8472-3c1130f6f088"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-O.rand.30__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ONA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ONA"," userResponse":" ONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-O.rand.30__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549455653290","data":{"timestamp":" 1549455653290"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_151651"," gameId":" 558dba72-b69b-45a3-8472-3c1130f6f088"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-O.rand.30__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ONA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ONA"," userResponse":" ONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-O.rand.30__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549455654915","data":{"timestamp":" 1549455654915"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_151651"," gameId":" 558dba72-b69b-45a3-8472-3c1130f6f088"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-O.rand.30__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" OFISI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OFISI"," userResponse":" OFISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-O.rand.30__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549455662921","data":{"timestamp":" 1549455662920"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_151651"," gameId":" 558dba72-b69b-45a3-8472-3c1130f6f088"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-O.rand.30__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" OFISI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OFISI"," userResponse":" OFISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-O.rand.30__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549455664553","data":{"timestamp":" 1549455664553"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_151651"," gameId":" 558dba72-b69b-45a3-8472-3c1130f6f088"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-O.rand.30__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" OGELEA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OGELEA"," userResponse":" OGELEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-O.rand.30__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549455671079","data":{"timestamp":" 1549455671079"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_151651"," gameId":" 558dba72-b69b-45a3-8472-3c1130f6f088"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-O.rand.30__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" OGELEA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OGELEA"," userResponse":" OGELEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-O.rand.30__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549455672713","data":{"timestamp":" 1549455672712"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_151651"," gameId":" 558dba72-b69b-45a3-8472-3c1130f6f088"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-O.rand.30__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" OSHA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OSHA"," userResponse":" OSHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-O.rand.30__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549455682118","data":{"timestamp":" 1549455682117"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_151651"," gameId":" 558dba72-b69b-45a3-8472-3c1130f6f088"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-O.rand.30__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" OSHA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OSHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-O.rand.30__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549455683730","data":{"timestamp":" 1549455683729"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_151651"," gameId":" 558dba72-b69b-45a3-8472-3c1130f6f088"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-O.rand.30__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" OMBA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OMBA"," userResponse":" OMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-O.rand.30__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549455688554","data":{"timestamp":" 1549455688554"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_151651"," gameId":" 558dba72-b69b-45a3-8472-3c1130f6f088"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-O.rand.30__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" OMBA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OMBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-O.rand.30__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549455690123","data":{"timestamp":" 1549455690123"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_151651"," gameId":" 558dba72-b69b-45a3-8472-3c1130f6f088"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-O.rand.30__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" OA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OA"," userResponse":" OA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-O.rand.30__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549455693318","data":{"timestamp":" 1549455693318"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_151651"," gameId":" 558dba72-b69b-45a3-8472-3c1130f6f088"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-O.rand.30__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" OA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-O.rand.30__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549455695329","data":{"timestamp":" 1549455695328"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_151651"," gameId":" 558dba72-b69b-45a3-8472-3c1130f6f088"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-O.rand.30__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" OA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549455695495","data":{"timestamp":" 1549455695495"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_151651"," gameId":" 558dba72-b69b-45a3-8472-3c1130f6f088"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-O.rand.30__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" OA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}